Guide to the Steve Waldron Papers 1976-1985
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Research Files, 1932-1985; Series III; 7.0 linear feet
  - Waitress Tips, HB 190, undated (Box-folder 21/17)
  - Wastewater, HB 207, undated (Box-folder 21/18)
  - Water Tax, HB 473, undated (Box-folder 21/19)
  - WETA, undated (Box-folder 21/20)
  - Water Quality, Environmental Administration, and Communicable Diseases, 1981 (Box-folder 22/1)
  - Welfare State Assumption, HB 798, undated (Box-folder 22/2)
  - Women's Corrections, undated (Box-folder 22/3)
  - Women's Rights, undated (Box-folder 22/4)
  - Workers' Compensation, HB 756, undated (Box-folder 22/5)
  - Workfare, HB 258, undated (Box-folder 22/6)
  - Work Privilege, Tax Inventory, undated (Box-folder 22/7)
  - YEP, undated (Box-folder 22/8)
  - Youth Court Commitment, SB 411, undated (Box-folder 22/9)
  - Youth Corrections, Mountain View, undated (Box-folder 22/10)
  - Youth Development, 1980 (Box-folder 22/11)
- Reports, undated; Series IV; 0.5 linear feet
  This series contains formal reports, usually from state administrative offices, that Steve Waldron collected during his tenure in the Montana State Legislature.
  - Deep Creek, undated (Box-folder 22/12)
  - Medicaid, undated (Box-folder 22/13)
  - Mountain View/Pine Hills Consolidation, undated (Box-folder 22/14)
  - Depreciation Allowance, HB 160, undated (Box-folder 23/1)
  - Prison Information, undated (Box-folder 23/2)
  - Prison Security Expansion, undated (Box-folder 23/3)
  - Public Employees Retirement Division, undated (Box-folder 23/4)
- Clippings, 1977-1983; Series V; 0.5 linear feet
  This series contains clippings from Montana newspapers that Steve Waldron collected during his tenure in the Montana State Legislature. Most of the clippings reference bills before the Legislature, issues related to legislation, and the Montana House of Representatives' operations. Some of the clippings directly reference Steve Waldron as a legislative member. From 1979 through 1983 clippings document issues of both legislative and personal interest to Mr. Waldron.
  - Legislature, 1977 (Box-folder 23/5)
  - Legislature, 1977 (Box-folder 23/6)
  - Legislature, 1977 (Box-folder 23/7)
  - Legislature, 1977 (Box-folder 23/8)
  - Legislature, 1977 (Box-folder 24/1)
  - General, 1979 (Box-folder 24/2)
  - General, 1981 (Box-folder 24/3)
  - General, 1983 (Box-folder 24/4)